components\modals\EvidexiaModal.js:                                    <p className="text-gray-600">AWS, Azure, GCP</p>
pages\MyQuest.js:      details: 'Raghunath Mashelkar originated the idea of "Gandhian Engineering" in 2008, which can be simply described as "getting more from less for more people." The concept draws inspiration from Mahatma Gandhi\'s teaching that the earth has enough resources to meet everyone\'s needs but not their greed. Unlike traditional innovation focused on profit, Gandhian Engineering aims to create products and services that deliver higher performance using fewer resources, at lower cost, and with less environmental impact making these innovations accessible and beneficial to a vast population, especially the underprivileged.',
pages\VoluntaryWork.js:                {/* AWS User Group UK Section */}
pages\VoluntaryWork.js:                                AWS User Group UK
pages\VoluntaryWork.js:                                I help coordinate events aimed at sharing deep technical insights, practical case studies, and real-world AWS implementation stories. My role includes supporting speakers, especially those from underrepresented backgrounds, curating session content, and maintaining strong community engagement. This work reflects my passion for improving cloud computing literacy across all skill levels.
pages\VoluntaryWork.js:                                href="https://www.meetup.com/awsuguk/members/?op=leaders"
